

# **Anushree Dhakate**

### **Talent Acquisition**

**Phone:** 8378024821, 8459647659 **Address:** Nagpur, Maharashtra, India

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/anushree-dhakate-1170871a8

Email: anushreedhakate28@gmail.com

Analytical and goal-driven Talent Acquisition Specialist with 2 years of experience sourcing top-grade candidates. Hands-on involvement in outlining job requirements, evaluating candidates, and projecting hiring needs. Brings exceptional organizational and communication skills, with a solid grasp of effective hiring platforms.

### **EXPERIENCE**

### **Vipsa Talent Solutions, Bangalore**

July 2022 - Present

### Talent Acquisition Specialist

- Handling end to end recruitment cycle starting from requisition, sourcing the candidates, short-listing, scheduling interviews, salary negotiation and final placement.
- Responsible for Permanent and Full Time Positions.
- Working on various onshore and offshore requirements.
- Sourcing the Relevant Profiles from the Various Job Portals as per the Requirements.
- Interacting with the candidates, giving them a brief about the position and checking them technically.
- Sourcing the candidate's right from different types of job portal like Naukri, Linked In, Indeed, Instahyre, Hirist etc.
- Briefing the candidates about the job profile, salary package, organization, etc...
- Scheduling and Tracking the Shortlisted Candidates for the Interview.
- Ensure the joining of offered candidates on the committed dates.
- Follow up the candidates till they complete all the rounds of interview.
- Follow up the selected candidates till they join to the requirement of the clients.
- Preparing and updating tracker of the selected candidates regarding their offer status and date of joining.
- Responsible for tracking the offered Candidates until Joins the Organization.
- Extensively used ATS (application tracking system) such as Icims, sap sucess factor, peoplestrong, cepial.
- Maintaining the different type of trackers& reports(Daily, weekly, Monthly).
- Maintain knowledge and understanding of information technology terminology.

# BRAINHUNT CONSULTANTS PRIVATE LIMITED, Nagpur

September 2021 - July 2022

### Recruiter

- Performing full life cycle recruiting including sourcing, posting jobs, candidate screening, extending offers, and assisting with workforce planning activities, and maintain excellent relations with hiring managers, candidates, and the community at-large.
- Run an end-to-end recruiting process from advertising positions to effectively screening candidates and moving them through a selection process, ending with the offer and on boarding process.
- Work with hiring managers to understand requirements and deliver against role specifications.
- Analysing job profiles/descriptions and candidate profiles/resumes to determine target profile needs and appropriate match.
- Sourcing candidates through proven recruitment channel including LinkedIn (Recruiter), Naukri, Referrals, Job posting and Internal Database.
- Interacting with stakeholders and technical teams to better understand the resource needs and hiring TAT.
- Understanding the business, Sourcing, Scheduling, Candidate engagement, HR discussions.
- Filling full time & Descriptions for different locations (Offshore/Onsite) in response to the project needs.
- Responsible for conducting and organizing phone, video and in-person

interviews.

- Conducting salary negotiation, preparing, and rolling out offer letters, following up till the Joining.
- Create/Develop and manage an effective Applicant Tracking System, to be able to track and report on all incoming applicants, as well as track metrics and use data for strategic analysis of recruiting campaigns.

### EDUCATION

# Dhananjayrao gadgil institute of cooperative management

January 2019 - December 2021

Master of Business Administration - MBA, human resource management and finance

• CGPA -8.79

# K. D. K COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING Nagpur Maharashtra

January 2014 - December 2018

bachelor of Engineering, electronics engineering

• Grade: 8.28

### SKILLS

- Communication Skills
- Client Relationship Management
- Complete life Cycle Recruitment
- Candidate Sourcing & Screening
- Lateral recruitment
- Social Media Recruiting Tools

### CERTIFICATIONS

# diploma in human resourses

May 2020 - Present

Alison - Free Online Learning

Credential ID: 167816035157

### **Human Resource Development**

NPTEI

Credential ID: NPTEL20HS48S62020663 Show Credential

# Managerial Skills with Interpersonal Dynamics

NPTEL.

Credential ID: NPTEL20MG08S12020024 Show Credential